# lason Hannanto

3001 Front St. Alhambra, CA 91803

🛘 (626) 267-6038 | 🗷 hannanto@usc.edu | 🌴 www.JasonHannanto.github.io | 🖸 JasonHannanto | 🛅 JasonHannanto

# Summary\_

Hi! My name is Jason. I'm currently a sophomore at the University of Southern California pursuing a B.S in Computer Science. Creating and perfecting a smooth and exciting user experience on a digital platform is my craft and I'm always excited to learn about new methods and technologies to better develop solutions.

## Education

### **University Of Southern California**

Los Angeles, CA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE

Expected Graduation: 2020

# Work Experience\_

#### **USC Davis School of Gerontology**

Los Angeles, CA Aug 2017 - Present

WEBMASTER

• Develop new web-pages utilizing HTML/CSS with Wordpress as a CMS.

- Maintain FTP-accessed servers through effective folder/file structures.
- Update and manage online courses through Blackboard/Coursesites.

#### **Reliant Pulmonary/Critical Care**

Monterey Park, CA

MEDICAL SCRIBE

Mar. 2016 - Aug 2017

- · Complete realtime/retrospective charting of patient encounters, including History of Present Illness, Review of Systems, Past Medical History, Family/Social History, Assessment (ICD-10 coding)/Plan, Vitals, Diagnostic Tests, and Medications.
- Setup and Navigation of EHR/Radiographic Imaging Software
- · Documentation/Transcription of Lab Results, Radiographic Imagery Reports, and procedural reports.

# **Projects**

### [Current] CollabSC

WEBSITE

- Online website that acts as a platform for USC students to connect and post projects to recruit other students.
- Created using Node.js, Express.js, MongoDB, as well as utilizing RESTful routing.

### [Current] CryptScreen

CRYPTOCURRENCY PRICE TRACKING

- Website that shows the biggest cryptocurrency prices realtime.
- Feeds prices through API connection from CoinMarketCap.

### Affiliation

### **Scope USC**

GENERAL MEMBER September 2017 - Present

• Scope is USC's Computer Science club where the top students come together to build, create, and learn new technologies and projects.

• Current Project: Node, Backend, Devops

### Skills

**Programming** C++, Python

**Frontend** HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Backend Node.js, Express.js Database NoSQL, MongoDB

Version Control Git

Paradigms REST, OOP, Unit Testing

JASON HANNANTO